Sis!
[Episode 4] What's the problem?
What's got your face all burning up?
Did you fart in front of Yun?
Hurry up and go! I need to pee, too!
Go to Yun's. I'm constipated.
What is it?
What should I do, Minchae?
Are you constipated, too?
There's a guy who came from Australia to see me.
What?
I met him when I followed Yun to shoot his ad.
He helped me out a lot.
You have a boyfriend?
No. I don't like him. He likes me.
He likes you but you don't like him?
Yeah.
It seems he's fallen for me.
I feel so sorry, what I should I do?
He's fallen for you...
So you're saying he's come all the way
from Australia for you.
Yes!
Did you sleep with him?
Huh?
Did you?
Yes.
I was freezing to death, so we held each other.
I think that's when he started to fall for me.
Are you crazy?
Oh my god...
It's always the quiet ones.
That's what I'm saying.
And it's you who did it, not me.
It's the end of the world as we know it.
No. It's not like that.
Oh, my...
Oh, how disgusting.
For how many hours have you guys
been talking here?
Sukchae, aren't you done?
Eunchae, Minchae. Aren't you done yet?
We are done. We'll be out soon.
Then come out.
Your father has to use the bathroom, too!
Mom!
What?
Eunchae said she slept with a guy.
I hear wedding bells.
No! We did sleep together but not in that way!
- What?
- No, no!
It's not like that!
Mom!
- Stop right there!
- Mom!
You, stop right there!
No, it's not like that!
Come here, Song Eunchae!
Why, you little!
No. It's not what you think!
I would never...
I haven't even had my first kiss!
Now I'm seeing things.
I feel so sorry.
- Eunchae!
- Going somewhere?
To see my brother.
- Your brother?
- Yes.
Oh. Have some.
What is this?
Mountain ginseng.
Huh?
They added some honey on the mountain ginseng
or something like that.
Eat it.
How can I eat such an expensive thing?
That's exactly why you should eat it.
I don't want to. Your mother bought it for you.
Hey, I can't eat this.
How could I? You eat it.
Then I'm going to feed it to the dogs.
Why can't you eat this?
My mouth is my mouth. Is your mouth dirty then?
Yun...
Give it so I can give it to the dog next door.
Hey, okay! I'll eat it.
- Better?
- Yes.
My mom says she feels the best
when she gives me good food.
I feel the best when I give you good food.
I must have been your mom or dad, in our past lives.
Eat well and grow up big and strong, okay?
- Son!
- Yes?
Yun, put this on and go.
What is that?
This is powdered pearl and mink oils.
It's great for crow's feet.
Where do I have crow's feet?
It's called prevention!
If you get so much as a single
mark on that face, I'll just die!
Eunchae, so what happened with that guy?
Guy?
Sure. Eunchae's got a boyfriend now.
Eunchae has a boyfriend?
Yes.
Who is it? What does he do?
He must be sensitive.
He likes her so much he was in tears.
Eunchae, be good.
If you make someone else cry,
then your eyes will cry blood.
Good luck, Eunchae.
Congratulations, you fake prude!
What on earth kind of guy is he?
Eunchae has awful standards when it comes to guys.
Why am I so upset?
Brother!
Get in!
I was...
Hey!
That's the kind of woman she is.
She'll destroy whatever's in her way.
Child, and everything. Toss it all out!
Water tastes great, doesn't it?
I had a cramp.
I almost died.
You can't let it know you fear it.
You have to win and stamp it out.
That's the only way you make friends with water.
- Brother.
- Yeah.
When'd you learn how to swim?
I didn't learn.
You weren't taught?
But I haven't learned, either.
Then what do I do to become as good as you?
Try your best!
Then I guess I should come here more often.
But I don't swim!
What are you doing?
You need to wash better!
Let me see your back.
When I think of my mother,
I feel grateful and I start to cry,
She gave birth to me, and raised me well.
And gives me endless love.
Mom, you are my sunshine. My world.
How is it?
It's good.
But this place...
It seems...
Look over here.
Stripes look great on Yun.
This is the fifth one, ma'am.
Oh, yeah?
This style wouldn't work on anyone but Yun, right?
Yeah, sure.
But, ma'am, this place is extremely expensive.
Red looks great on my son as well.
One second...
Having a great son is hard work, too.
Yes, manager.
Yun? You can't reach him?
He said he was going to meet up with his "brother."
I don't know what he was talking about.
Newspapers?
No, I didn't see them.
What?
["Choi Yun Got Used by Kang Minju!]
["Kang Minju reveals all:
Love's just a game to me, I was only playing"]
"Out of rice?"
I have to go somewhere. I'll see you later.
"You're going to drive drunk?"
"Let me see your license!"
Your head won't bust that way. Want a hammer?
I'm going to kill myself and her today.
No one better stop me.
Come in, Eunchae! Door's open!
Wait, just one more round...
This is a false report, right?
Go clear it up with Yun.
It came out exactly as I said in the interview.
You wanna die?
You wanna get beaten?
Do you have any idea how much Yun loves you?
Yun's different from all your other guys!
Sorry.
It's just how I am.
You know I'm a flirt by nature.
Why do you live this way, huh? Why?
You're better than that!
Is this the way you want to live, you brat?
Why do you live so recklessly? Want to end your career?
Are you a blockhead? Are you an idiot?
Why do stupid things willingly?
Have you decided to end it all?
You idiot, you dummy, you moron!
You done hitting me?
Is that all you've got?
You should break my rib or something.
Yun... I think I like him.
I think because of that...
Maybe because I was really starting to like him...
That's why I did it.
What?
You like Yun, don't you?
Hey!
I've got a PhD in relationships.
You think I wouldn't know? I've known for a long time.
Who's heard of a friendship between a guy and a girl?
What on earth are you talking about?
Do you really want to get smacked today?
Still, I wanted to play dumb and go all the way,
but I couldn't because of you.
You have him.
You can have him.
That's right. You should get smacked.
You need a beating bring get you back to your senses.
I'm going to break your ribs and your legs!
You're dead meat, Kang Minju!
Can't you stop that, Eunchae?
What do you think you're doing?
Are you a thug?
What gives you the right to hit her?
- No one lays a finger on her!
- Yun!
Mind your own business from now on.
Don't meddle in ours, Eunchae.
Don't overreact.
You got it?
- Get out!
- Yun!
Didn't you hear me? Get out of this house!
Eunchae!
I'll definitely break your ribs next time.
Eunchae...
Don't let anyone hit you.
Not me.
Not Eunchae. No one.
If someone does this again,
I'm going to kill them.
Be it Eunchae, or myself.
I'll kill them all.
Don't do anything you'll get hit for.
You'll die too.
And I'll die.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I won't be that way again. I'm sorry.
Poor baby.
Are you lost?
Don't cry. Don't cry, okay?
I'll find your mother for you.
Good girls don't cry.
Santa Claus doesn't give presents to children who cry.
So don't cry.
Hello?
Is this Saetbyul's mother?
Hi, I'm Song Eunchae.
Bye!
What's the capital of Australia?
You don't know your country's capital?
Canberra.
Isn't it Sydney?
When did it change?
What about the capital of Korea?
Seoul.
So you're not crazy.
Then fine. Let's go out.
Are you embarrassed?
Are you too shy to look me in my face?
You're introverted, I see.
I didn't think so.
Say "ahh."
Don't be embarrassed.
This is what couples do when they go out.
It's called being affectionate.
Ahh!
Are you being shy again?
You're so cute.
Please be quiet.
What?
I'll be asleep for five minutes, so please...
Be quiet.
Okay.
Oh my gosh.
Are you okay?
Hey! Wake up, sir!
Wow, a golden egg!
Have some.
It's okay. You eat it.
Eat it!
I don't eat food others ate.
But Eunchae does.
She has the stomach for that.
- Am I a stranger?
- Sorry.
It's just how I am.
I don't even eat my mother's leftovers.
Where are you going?
The bathroom.
Did you get home safe, Eunchae?
About before...
I was out of line.
You're not upset, are you?
Actually, I didn't mean to take it out on you.
Why isn't she answering?
Hello?
Hello? Isn't this Song Eunchae's cell phone?
The owner has fainted.
What?
Her dad said he's on his way.
Where is she?
Sir, sir! Please wake up.
They must have drank a lot.
Are you okay?
They won't even budge.
Pardon me!
Excuse me.
They astonishingly fainted while kissing.
Eunchae!
It's your dad!
Eunchae! Your dad is here.
She's sound asleep.
She passes out like this when she's drunk.
I see.
Eunchae!
I can't pull them apart.
Isn't that Choi Yun?
Yun!
What happened?
These two were drinking and then they kissed and...
Hey! Help me.
Get up!
Help me lift her.
What happened?
How did Muhyeok and Eunchae end up together?
Is he someone you know?
Yes.
How do you know him?
He's like my brother.
What does he do?
I'm not sure.
Yun!
Yes?
What are some things Eunchae likes?
Chicken feet, shellfish, crackers and rice.
What doesn't she like?
Ghosts, orangutans, hospitals, spicy noodles.
Why do you ask?
Because I'm her father...
Yet I don't know a thing about her.
You've spent more time with her than me, right?
Yes.
You probably know her more than I do. Right?
Is Eunchae...
Yes?
Promiscuous?
What?
Good night!
You rascal.
What? Let go.
You're so strange.
Mom said to fold the blankets!
Just leave it. I'll fold it later.
What? Did you wet the bed?
Minchae, conference time!
What?
What secret is it that
we have to be under the covers?
I'm late for school.
Who brought me home yesterday?
Dad did.
Mom's having a fit because of you
so run like hell when you see her.
Would... Would you look at my lips?
What about them?
How are my lips? Does it look they've been kissed?
What?
I'm not sure if it was a dream or not.
I can't tell.
Look at them.
Do they look like they've been kissed?
What do kissed lips look like anyway?
I wouldn't know. Since I've never kissed anyone.
What did you do yesterday?
I know, right?
But you've read a lot of weird books,
so wouldn't you know?
I wouldn't know, either...
Want me to get the magnifying glass?
Your lips seem bruised and swollen.
Push them out more.
According to my calculations, you did kiss.
What am I going to do?
They say the body remembers what your brain doesn't.
Do it again so we can confirm our findings. With him.
What?
Kiss.
Are you crazy?
Not for anything dirty. Just forget it!
Hey! Ouch!
I'm not liking these dishes.
Where might the Italian china be?
Don't move a step!
Who are you?
You're hurt, stay still!
Aren't you Eunchae's boyfriend?
But why are you here?
Where's the medicine?
Yun!
Son!
Yun is asleep!
Where's the medicine?
Yun!
What's going on?
Who is that man?
Who? Ah, that's Muhyeok.
Why is he at our house?
I brought him over last night. He was too drunk.
I told you not to bring just anyone in!
But he was drunk and we don't know where he lives.
You don't know where he lives?
You don't even know him well!
Why bring him here? Are you a common man?
You're a celebrity!
Quiet. He'll hear us.
Who do you take after that you can act this way?
Since you're my mother, I probably take after you.
I got to take a leak, I'll be back.
That guy scares me. Tell him to leave, please.
What's scary about him? He won't bite.
I'm going to wash, so just stay around.
Hey!
Then I'll go with you to the bathroom.
Were you hurt?
Yeah, I was hurt a lot. I'm bleeding.
You're driving me crazy.
Let's put some medicine on it.
- Stop!
- No!
Let me borrow this for a while.
Am I a joke to you? Do I look like a pushover?
If you show up again, you're dead meat!
Hey, hey!
Will she be okay?
She'll be fine. It was a good thing
to stop her bleeding.
Seaweed rolls for sale!
Seaweed rolls for sale! Rice cakes for sale!
Rice cakes for sale! Seaweed rolls for sale!
Rice cakes for sale!
Seaweed rolls!
Seaweed rolls for sale!
How's business?
- Hey!
- Hi!
You're bleeding!
You should go the hospital.
Why did you tell me?
My mother... Why did you tell me about her?
What did you expect me to do about it?
What do you want me to do about it, you old man?
Do whatever you want.
Whatever you want.
All done. Go to the hospital.
My mother...
That lady...
Did she wrong you, too?
Yes.
Galchi, let's have dinner together tonight.
- Let's make galchi fish.
- Okay.
Kang Minju has publicly declared
her relationship with Choi Yun.
I've had a crush on her every day
for the past three years
For her alone, I can give up everything in the world.
Without her, I don't feel alive.
What are your feelings toward Choi Yun?
Choi Yun is the nicest and most purehearted man I know.
I've done him a lot of wrong,
But I'm determined to make it up to him.
I didn't think love was real,
But through Yun, I've come to believe in it.
I'm so happy and I support him.
I trust and respect my son's decision
one hundred percent.
If Yun chose her, I'm sure she's a good girl.
I'm going to love her like a daughter.
He's scary. Just tell him to leave.
Yun!
Son!
Do whatever you want.
Both of them have opened their hearts
and the public agrees they match well.
They're rising in popularity.
Due to today's conference,
fans are reacting hugely.
Live happily, Yun!
If you hurt him, I'll make sure you pay, Minju!
Be happy together!
I've got to go to the studio.
I don't think I can drive you.
It's okay. That's why I brought my car.
I'll call you. Get home safe.
How can I help you?
Hey!
Lady! Get out.
"Lady"?
[Episode 5 Preview]
- What, mom?
- So sue me!
I'll go on the blind date.
Tell me the truth.
What exactly don't you like about me?
I really don't like how you look.
Lady! Get out.
Are you trying to hit on me?
- Do you like me too?
- No!
Then why poke a man minding his own business?
I'm going to tell my son and have this place torn down
and have a new building built on top of it.
What are you doing? Stop!
How would it feel to be up there?
Would it look much better than it does from here?
If you're so curious, then why don't you go?
I'll be going there soon.